

# Iman MAMMADLI

**Date of birth:** 02/06/1999 | **Phone number:** (+994) 558189498 (Mobile) | **Email address:** 

imanmemmedoglu@gmail.com | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/imanmammadli/

Address: AZ1021, Baku, Azerbaijan (Home)

## ABOUT ME

Hi. My name is Iman and I am pursuing a career in Data Science. I have a strong foundation with my Computer Engineering and Data Science degrees. My ability to think analytically, understand data and draw meaningful conclusions and develop ideas that can be integrated into the business world reflects my commitment to data science. I am focused on continuous learning and self-improvement and aim to specialize in data science and analysis.

### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

15/09/2013 - 30/05/2017 Baku, Azerbaijan

HIGH SCHOOL EDUCATION BAKU TURKISH ANATOLIAN HIGH SCHOOL

Website https://btal.meb.k12.tr/

27/09/2017 - 29/07/2022 Samsun, Türkiye

**COMPUTER ENGINEER - BACHELOR'S DEGREE** ONDOKUZ MAYIS UNIVERSITY

Website https://www.omu.edu.tr/tr/hakkimizda/iletisim

01/10/2022 - CURRENT Samsun, Türkiye

**DATA SCIENCE - MASTER DEGREE** ONDOKUZ MAYIS UNIVERSITY

Website https://www.omu.edu.tr/tr/hakkimizda/iletisim

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

01/02/2022 - 15/05/2022 Samsun, Türkiye

#### FULL STACK GAME DEVELOPER ONDOKUZ MAYIS UNIVERSITY

The work included the development of online VR museums and custom VR simulations. In this job, I was both a team management and full-stack game developer. This project I did at the university was both my end-of-term project and a task given by the university.

The technologies used in this process are Google Cardboard, the tools used are Unity Game Engine, Autodesk 3Ds Max, Visual Studio.

01/08/2023 - CURRENT Baku, Azerbaijan

# **DATA ANALYST XALQ INSURANCE**

Data Warehousing.

Installation and configuration of power bi server.

SQL Queries, Exploring Data, Creating views, Data cleaning.

Creating Server-Excel connections and creating Excel reports.

Preparation of power bi reports with time-independent excel data.

Preparation and installation of power bi incremental and of real-time reports.

Preparation of power bi reports with server connections and installation of real-time reports.



# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **AZERBAIJANI** | **TURKISH** 

Other language(s): **ENGLISH (B2)** 

### DIGITAL SKILLS

**Programming Languages & Skills** 

C Programming | Python | R Programming | Clean Code | Object-Oriented Programming

**Data Visualization** 

Power BI | Power BI Report Builder | Power BI Server | R ggplot2 | Python Matplotlib

**Data Tools** 

Data Warehouse | MS Excel | SQL | T-SQL | MySQL | MS SQL Server | PostgreSQL | R dplyr | Python Pandas | Python Numpy | NoSQL | SSIS | SSRS

Web Scrape

Web Scraping | HTML | CSS | Selenium | Python BeautifulSoup

**Software Development Systems** 

Jupyter Notebook | Visual Studio | Git | Github